okay
let's get back to where we were
did i not make a script to compile this
hello
thank you
yeah i'm in the gray shirt uh
no i got it i got a date tonight so
we did four loops it's done
we did that one
so there's a few things we could do
today
if you recall on the last stream
we uh
no i'm not i gotta get changed before
the date
i'm learning how to clean clothes too we
gotta i gotta do laundry soon
hello hello
here i am at camp granada that one
uh online
let's just say in new york there's many
women
which isn't true about now there's many
women everywhere
but they're easier
the ratios are better in new york city
uh no i'm not streaming my date for you
guys
does it really make me look zuckerbergy
damn new york city
no i didn't watch the any trust hearing
i don't care
uh i can't believe i watched five
minutes of the
impeachment shit the kavanaugh shit
it's it's just don't watch it
the only the only solution
to today's uh
attention-seeking world where everything
is infused with power
is to turn it off
um now i have some i have some excerpts
from this book that i'm going to read to
you guys but
we need i think we need quiet um
this book's called white noise by don
deleo and let's see if i can i can find
there were a few i should have
highlighted you know
all about the wonderfulness of
supermarkets
i should really highlight things there's
a few things in here that i would just
like
should we just do a reading stream
do a story
oh yeah yeah this this this whole thing
was pretty good
i asked him why is it alphonse that
decent well-meaning and responsible
people find themselves intrigued by
catastrophe when they see it on
television
i told them about the recent evening of
lava mud and raging water
the children and i had found so
entertaining
we wanted more more it's natural it's
normal you said with a reassuring nod it
happens to everybody
why because we're suffering from brain
fade
we need an occasional catastrophe to
break up the incessant bombardment of
information
it's obvious lasher said a slight man
with a taut face and slicked back hair
the flow is constant said alphonse words
pictures numbers facts graphics
statistics specs waves particles moats
only a catastrophe gets our attention we
want them we need them we depend on them
as long as they happen somewhere else
that's where california comes in
mudslides brush fires coastal erosion
earthquakes mass killings etc
we can relax and enjoy these disasters
because in our hearts
we feel that california deserves what it
gets californians invented the concept
of lifestyle
that alone warrants their doom
kozakus crushed a can of diet pepsi and
threw it at a garbage pail
japan is pretty good for disaster
footage alfons said india remains
largely untapped
they have tremendous potential with
their famines monsoons religious strife
train wrecks boat sinkings etc
but their disasters tend to go
unrecorded their lines in the newspaper
no film footage no satellite hookup
that's why california is so important
we not only enjoy seeing them punished
for their relaxed lifestyle and
progressive social ideas
but we know that we're not missing
anything the cameras are right there
they're standing by
nothing terrible escapes their scrutiny
you're saying
it's more or less universal to be
fascinated by tv disasters
for most places for most people there
are only two places in the world
where they live and their tv sets if a
thing happens on television we have
every right to find it fascinating
whatever it is
um i've i've really been enjoying this
book that's what i've been doing uh
this morning reading this book
i will do one more
everything is concealed in symbolism
hidden by veils of mystery and layers of
cultural material
but it is psychic data absolutely the
large doors slide open they close
unbidden
energy waves incident radiation all the
letters and numbers are here all the
colors of the spectrum
all the voices and the sounds all the
code words and ceremonial phases
phrases it's just a question of
deciphering rearranging and peeling off
the letters of unspeakability
not that we would want to not that there
is any useful purpose to be observed
this is not tibet even tibet is not to
bed anymore
studied her profile she put some yogurt
in the cart
tibetans try to see death for what it is
it is the end of an attachment to things
the simple truth is hard to fathom
but once we stop denying death we can
perceive calmly to die and then go on to
experience uterine rebirth or
the judeo-christian afterlife or
out-of-body experiences with a trip on a
ufo or whatever we wish to call it
we can do so with clear vision without
awe or terror
we don't have to cling to life
artificially or to death for that matter
we simply walk toward the sliding doors
waves and radiation
look at how well lighted everything is
the place is sealed off self-conscious
it is timeless
another reason why i think of tibet
dying is an art in tibet
a priest walks in sits down tells the
weeping relatives to get out and has the
room sealed
doors windows sealed he has serious
business to see to
chance numerology horoscopes
resuscitations
here we don't die we shop but the
difference is less market than you think
he was almost whispering now and i was
trying to get up closer without ramming
my car into the vets
i wanted to hear everything supermarkets
this large and clean and modern are a
revelation
to me i spent my life in small steamy
delicatessens with slanted display
cabinets full of trays that hold wet
loft sumpy
soft wet lumpy matter and pale colors
high enough cabinets so you had to stand
on tiptoes to give your order
shouts accents in cities no one notices
specific dying
dying is a quality of the air it is
everywhere in nowhere men shout as they
die to be noticed remembered for a
second or two
to die in an apartment instead of a
house can depress the soul i would
imagine for several lives to come
in a town there are houses plants and
bay windows people notice
dying better the dead have faces
automobiles
if you don't know a name you know a
street name a dog's name he drove an
orange mazda you know a couple useless
things about a person
that become major facts of
identification and cosmic placement when
he dies suddenly
after a short illness in his own bed
with comforter and matching pillows
on a raining wednesday afternoon
feverish a little congested in the
sinuses and chest
thinking about his dry cleaning
don delilah white voice
i haven't read the whole book yet but
so that's that's what we're doing today
we
i mean my phone black and white
i find a lot of uh old philosophy hard
to get into i mean some things are
accessible
nietzsche is somewhat accessible
kierkegaard wrote a few good short
stories i don't know if you count
kafka's philosophy but if you ask me to
read heidegger
and or heggle and learn about da sign
and fuck that shit man that's not even
anything
no if you can't understand it you have
two choices you can either say
you know it's because they're saying
something deep and mystical
um or you can say it's because this is
actually just you know
non-existent uh no i can't understand it
nickel is clearly a charlotte and i
agree and you have guys like
foucault who basically admitted they
were charlatans
[Music]
it's not even anything george hats
um i don't know
oh shit yeah i've
uh it's too contemporary
kind of um
hey george i coded my own two state two
symbol busy beaver to understand the
problem one nice job
um
i read the stranger back in the day i
found it hard
to get through though i think now i
could probably read kamu
sar no exit's one of my favorite stories
um
i don't think they're all fake no i
don't have a test prepared today i don't
really have much prepared today
i guess i more wanted to complain about
philosophy than code
um i did not watch the congress hearing
i am absolutely done
with anything these people have to say
it's all fake
it's all stage work you're watching a
shitty movie
every time you watch one of these
congressional hearings you're watching a
shitty
movie that has nothing to do with the
levers of power in this country
and have everything to do with
entertaining and placating you
should we just do philosophy well what
should we read
what lecon should be i i've heard of
this guy i dated this girl
listen to these people adorno
uh and they were
she opened my mind to a lot of stuff
now the myth of sisyphus
i don't know i'm not sure i really feel
like like
here's here's here's maybe this is just
talking stream
um it's a conversation
uh
i thought about it yesterday i thought
about yesterday's stream i i even
rewatched parts of yesterday's stream
uh smoking weed streams um
i don't know why do i want a blue check
mark on instagram why do i want to be a
twitch partner
it just seems like these are things that
other people
want so like getting them has
uh has value but
maybe not um i was reading uh
this girl's blog um
no what's her uh
like knowingless it's it's the cowgirl
blog
that i read off of before um
and i found some of these uh
posts to be really interesting
she speaks here about enlightenment
and she goes and asks people uh
instead of asking the question whether
people are enlightened or not
um she gets at what enlightenment means
she asks what does enlightenment mean
and
yeah she breaks it down and she talks
kind of about these four things
um material enlightenment
these people sound like a in an
inspirational talk given by a competent
ceo at a dinner party
skill enlightenment which is like
whether you can meditate and do brain
tricks
warp reality in your mind standard
enlightenment which is the usual
you know peace wordlessness no self and
understanding
uh traditional enlightenment it's just
it was an interesting
um breakdown
of what it means to be honest i
did some reflecting last night and i was
thinking really just what i want is
is worthwhile uh
worthwhile competitions to win
you know what what is is it really
worthwhile to
uh become a twitch streamer or an
instagram influencer
i mean you know what's the top it's the
top profession now
that kids want to be uh american kids
used to want to grow up to be astronauts
now they want to grow up to be uh to be
influencers
i was on this uh this date with this
other girl and i was like telling her
like
look these kids don't actually grow up
to be influencers nobody does
these jobs are dependent on fame
probably similar you know you want to be
logan paul that's as far as being an
astronaut
um
i think so uh i'm scared to google it
because
what else i was googling i was trying to
find some uh
i was reading it's like some like
rationalist blog where it linked to this
other blog and like that he was like
like
this is what the red pill people
actually believe and i searched for that
phrase on google and i got news articles
and i was upset
um
why are you driven by competition and
not intrinsically
uh you know we're just going to change
this to
to talking hour because i don't know i
feel like coding
i did a contract the beginning of this
week
yeah i made a good amount of money i
paid for
my apartment my lavish stay
in new york city
a 420 lmao here's your recognition
uh i didn't like the matrix two and
three i can really get through
um i don't know who dr k is i'm not
talking to destiny
i also took i took a big five uh yeah
i'll do it on stream they're kind of fun
um
[Music]
so i i did i did this this morning a big
five personality test
i'm the life of the party i'd say
somewhat
i feel little concern for others that's
probably true
i'm always prepared no i get stressed
out easily not really
i have a decently rich vocabulary i talk
a lot
i'm not that interested in people um
i don't really leave my belongings
around i'm relaxed most of the time
i understand abstract ideas pretty well
i feel comfortable around people
sometimes i insult people
yeah maybe
pay attention to details not really i
don't really worry about things
i have a vivid imagination i keep in the
background
um i don't know i did this test
uh the big five personality
um
yeah i found out i had very low
agreeableness
i had high openness medium
conscientiousness high extroversion
low agreeableness and low neuroticism
uh so i don't know i don't know what
that that says about me and then i
looked into like agreeableness
um then i looked into like
like dark triad behavior you know you
read about this stuff before i don't
know
i mean am i these people i don't know
i do score very low on agreeableness
um
think that i think that a lot of these
people are
am i going mad no
i i don't know i don't think zuckerberg
deserves all the hate he gets
um
what do you do if you're mark zuckerberg
specializes on the oh let's see what
does this word mean
influence of others instead of allowing
them to come to their own conclusion
yeah uh
i do lizard people things
how does he drink the water
um i've met real mark zuckerberg several
times
he's been coached a lot now
the water drinking test
it's cuz i'm wearing the gray shirt yeah
this is live
i refreshed it to get the viewer count i
don't know why it doesn't sync
i drove from the tab
um i have a really low standard of
living
we can go back we can go back to the we
can work on busy beaver
i mean it's kind of interesting but
really what i want to discover is like
busybeaver52 might be worthwhile
who made this fucking subreddit
it's better than a discord i'm telling
you if i ever see a discord
if anyone makes a discord and starts
talking in it and i find out about it
we're going to uh we're going to stop
streaming that's the end of it
then it got too big
the subreddit's somewhat okay
um we're not gonna we're not gonna
scream about the subreddit
yo if i find out about a discord
seriously one asshole's gonna ruin it
no i don't have a discord if there's a
discord
yeah no just i mean you know what like
like yeah there might be there might be
uh
for you know really if this if this
becomes a big thing it's it's over
there are zero discourse that's what i
like to hear uh
i'm fairly anti-discord yeah
oh there's a discord
with 70 people in it um i'm serious
uh
all right shut it down
uh if you don't i really i just won't
stream anymore
um you better delete it
if i find it that's it that's it that's
the end of the streams
um no slacks no discord
nothing real time the stream exists when
it's here it doesn't exist when it's not
here
i give you a lot of power yeah i mean
you guys are welcome look if
like i don't know i don't really know um
now people are gonna start making
discords but we'll see you know that's
it that's the end of it
uh that'd be like oh cool yep he was a
streamer for a bit but
now he's not a now he's not a stream
anymore
do i exist if i stop the stream not to
you
how do you know i'm not already a uh
a gpg3 what if some of these streams are
in me
you know what if some of these streams
are just i trained uh
i trained an ai on the thousands of
hours of content and it's like deep
fakes
you did you would have a better haircut
now it's so easy for one person to ruin
it i mean that's how it is
you know you guys can self police though
you guys can self police
and i believe i believe in you
uh you can have merch but you have to
make it yourself
anybody who's selling merch get fucked
um
i would just quit if this if this like
became like a bigger thing i would quit
uh like it comes down fundamentally to
whether i think i get value from it or
not it's it's an interesting way to
self-reflect
um i can talk with you
and then in effect almost running the
filter that i run on myself
when i'm streaming allows me to
uh access
parts of my mind that i wouldn't it also
when i use it to code
um it's it's kind of easier to decode in
front of a in front of an audience it's
a different state of mind
uh and it's an interesting it's a way to
access it
therapy hour yeah this is therapy i was
thinking about that this morning
i was thinking about you know people can
come to my apartment and
i'll talk with them about their problems
for an hour
uh but then i realized that i don't have
a license
and it's probably illegal i don't really
know why it's illegal
and then i didn't really look more into
it because i realized that you know
what am i going to say to these people i
don't really know
you know what if what if what if one of
them takes my advice and kills
themselves
i just don't know if i could deal with
that so so it's not worth it
um talk to dr k no i've been through a
lot of therapy in my life
uh
coaching yeah yeah coach got a good
point yeah if i dress it up in some
euphemistic terms it's all legal
um
yeah maybe i mean i wouldn't do it you
know for everything i do
under my name there's a whole set of
things that i don't do under my name
and like this would be one of those
projects
um it definitely wouldn't be no because
we'd get fucking fanboys man
like fanboys are real like like people
go people go stupid in the mind when
they get into fanboy mode
you know oh we can talk about deep shit
on the stream
yeah i think it mostly is listening
no if geo streams stop i mean you know
guys and like
i i had i had a big twitter file i had
150k followers on twitter and like
you know people pissed me off so i
deleted it to be honest
uh and i'll do the same
uh no it's never worth cashing out what
do you think you're getting
century of self
i mean that's that's an interesting
quote this series is about how those in
power have used freud's theories to try
to control the dangerous crowd in the
major mass democracy
um you know what was what was that thing
that i went to it was like uh
safety.google or something yeah
um remember we looked at this yesterday
on the stream
and like i i just
i don't understand the person who reads
this
and like not only
i look at this and i can't tell you
whether this is true
or not all i can say about it
is that it was written by a pr person
google hired somebody and
they don't know anything about how
google was founded anything more than
you might find by reading wikipedia
um and their job of course is to write
nice sounding copy for this website
uh so this isn't true or
false it's it's it's gpt three level
shit
um i think i forget which maybe it was
on hacker news where people were talking
about
what if you seriously you always want to
talk about gpg3 here you go
what if you seriously scale up gpg3
how many jobs can it replace i think i
think there was a thing where someone
tried to use like gpk3 as a design
brand consultant and like it did pretty
well
um
no of course i get trash
honestly half the time i use google to
try to find things that i've already
visited
i could be better about this uh
design brand consultant it was like a
fake chair company
no it's not see
never mind i i can't find it but
um i i don't know
you think they're gonna give me the beta
key
you think let's let's let's let's go to
the gp3 beta
let's let's you want to try to apply
let's try to apply
join the waitlist i'm interested in
being a beta user of the api
name my name is george my email is
geohotogmail.com
um your use case please
provide a
brief description of the way that you or
your organization might want to use the
api
where applicable please include any
initial thoughts you have around
any potential benefits or risks from
your use case or other information that
you'd like us to know
um i think it was nips
paper uh
society impact their
um
you know these these
these people this is this is no sorry
nips has been renamed to nurips
um these people are demanding that
your your ai paper have a section about
broader impact
this work has the following potential
positive impact in the society
at the same time the work may have some
negative consequences because
furthermore we should be cautious of the
result of failure of the system which
could cause
um
i i i
who who pushes this stuff
you know
um jordan peterson
i don't wanna you know i wanna be jordan
peterson jordan peterson on sick leave
you know i can look into that more i
don't think he's on sick leave
uh you don't wanna be famous man you
really don't
um you know you think you do and you
think you want to get your ideas out
there but your ideas are just going to
be
yeah i like i like this quote i like
this quote from century of the self
um this is about how those in power have
used for its theories to try to control
the dangerous crowd it's the same
it's it's the same with with with jordan
peterson or with anything that becomes
popular it's not going to um
it's it's not going to be interpreted
the way uh the person wanted to be
interpreted and then
you think about things that cannot be
interpreted wrong and i think this is
one of the beauties of crypto
bitcoin as speech you can't misinterpret
bitcoin it is exactly what it is it's
the greatest threat to state
power um that has come around in the in
the in this century
is it possible to discern between crappy
writing and gpd3 writing no
oh oh we're going to build detection
models
yeah um i mean you can do that for
imagenet right
you could build you could build a
detection model for imagenet and you
could detect uh
whether or not
the imagenet classification results are
being done by a human or being done by
a machine
to read the unibomber manifesto on
stream see today it's political
it was never really intended to be
political i mean in in
in a way like
they would reference it a lot on consume
product and then
in a way you you realize that consumed
product is
does irony make it okay
i think i used to think that i think i
used to think that
having these views ironically
was okay i don't really think that
anymore
i think whether you're doing it
ironically or not the intent doesn't
really matter
and the right thing to do is just not
have the views at all
oh whoops i actually didn't mean to deny
that um
i i i meant to accept that and yeah to
say
look you know i got an email this
morning uh from a hedge fund that wants
to buy common ai
so you know you never you never turn
rich people down you always just say how
much and of course they're not giving
you a real answer they're going to ask
for a phone call and that's going to be
the end of that conversation
um but shit man you know if they said 2
billion you know that's my number voice
um and then we'll start you know
uh david foster wallace on irony
maybe not
yeah so so like like new sincerity uh
the this word popped into my mind i was
into david foster walls for a bit
um i read some pale king excerpts on my
instagram
uh infinite jest is one of my favorite
books
um
ah let's read this essay together that
sounds somewhat nice
is it short
that's not social watching
i will read this i don't want to i'll
read this on my own time
yeah post-post-modernism
the next real literary rebels in this
country might well emerge as some
weird bunch of anti-rebels born oglers
who dare somehow to back away from my
ironic watching who have the childish
goal actually to endorse
and instantiate single entendre
principles
who treat of plain old untrendy human
troubles and emotions in u.s life with
reverence and conviction
who issues self-consciousness and hip
fatigue these anti-rebels will be
outdated of course before they even
started dead on the page too sincere
clearly repressed
backward quaint naive anachronistic
maybe that'll be the point
maybe that'll be why they're the next
real rebels real rebels as far as i can
see risk disapproval
the old postmodern insurgents risked the
grasp and squeal
shock disgust outrage censorship
accusations of socialism anarchism
nihilism
today's risks are different the new
rebels might be artists willing to risk
the yawn the rolled eyes the cool smile
the nudge ribs
the parody of gifted ironists the
ohabanal
to risk accusations of sentimentality
melodrama of over credulity
of softness of willingness to be
suckered into a world of lurkers and
stairs who fear gaze and ridicule
above imprisonment without law who knows
yeah i i mean i completely agree i i
think that
the question is where do they succeed
right
where where do these these these people
succeed
not in industries that are controlled by
social media
um social media
uh
here's here's something i was thinking
about this morning actually started i
was
listening to some beats and i was
working on some diss tracks
and i was like who do i dislike and i
realized a group of people that i
dislike are internet commenters
no internet commenters are not the
majority of people
i have really never commented on
anything on the internet
i don't have a reddit account um my
facebook account was
was largely full of uh banal bullshit
um i i do these videos but these videos
are
and the one requirement that i make for
these videos and i will issue takedowns
to anybody who tries to do otherwise
is that the videos be presented in full
with context
um because if you're willing to watch a
multi-hour video
you won't take me out of context
you won't take a
one sentence snippet and and take that
snippet and figure out how that works
into whatever your ideological world
view is
you'll have to if you want
access to this content well you know
watch the video
um
[Music]
social media has consequences have been
a disaster for the human race
well this
uh black mirror is probably the
appropriate answer to that
social media is not you can say social
media is the problem
um you can say
one group one political group is the
problem
uh you can say that if only everybody
thought this way
well yeah but what you're really getting
at is inability to solve
like coordination problems if
it makes sense for everybody to defect
there is no more power in the world
i think that the the poor believe that
they have no options in life and you'll
hear this is a common
kind of is the word respite is that the
word i intend to use
yeah yeah a common respite of the
respite of the poor is that
oh well you know circumstances
circumstances and circumstances
um and if if someone who's rich or
powerful tried to say that
uh they wouldn't be accepted as sincere
but in reality it's unclear that they
have more freedom of action than the
poor person
in some ways they may have less
uh something that i did realize early on
with with kind of
comma uh and and my life in general
is if you're a celebrity who's known for
doing
one thing you don't have
power you actually because well you may
have power you may have
influence but if you have no freedom to
go with that power and influence you
have nothing
and that's i think a lot of people
who've gotten to quote-unquote high up
positions
they're there on very tight leashes and
these leashes are being held by all the
other people in these positions
um it's true the more successful the
less free
uh i mean i value freedom above
success by far so i'm gonna try to beat
that
like to answer the question more
concretely about why
if this stream ever became popular we'd
have to shut it down it's for that
reason
how free am i i mean starting combo was
one of the biggest things i did which
limits my freedom
but it doesn't really limit my freedom
it's a prison that i've made for myself
of course when you want to start
something
will we win self-driving cars
i did this i did this ethereum contract
um
over the last three days and it feels
nice it feels nice it feels nice to
to step in on problems that people have
been working on for a long time and
solve them relatively quickly
but yeah i mean you know when my
competition is is is
uh you know a classic like startup it's
not that
hard uh to to to do really well
and to this self-driving car is maybe
um here uh so
curtis paul graham response
uh if you read the paul graham uh
gray mirror hologram um
here open letter to paul graham uh
if you read the the the paul graham
essay and then i also read
it was like another thing posted on
hacker news
which was uh against this
this is i mean this is against this from
a different angle and then
there was another one that was against
this too if you haven't read the essay i
mean it went around the internet it was
pretty popular
but i think there was one the one line
that i want to quote
um paul graham says but i'm hopeful long
term and uh curtis replies with i'm not
the only thing we have to fear is hope
itself for of all the impediments to
success false hope is by far the
deadliest
false hope trains you on a low bar you
see that bar and think
that's not too bad i can work out more
stop eating carbs i can clear it
you do the work you practice you clear
the bar every time then in the real
event you see
the real bar higher than you can ever
imagine and you just walk back to the
locker room
um the thing that
i immediately associate with this isn't
he speaks more about the political
situation i don't even associate it with
that i associate this with the rise of
ai
um the singularity happened five years
ago
the computers run society the twitter
algorithm runs society just because the
computers leech
off of human intelligences in order to
do it maybe the singularity happened
once megacorps existed
when when humans are no longer the
dominant species on the planet
um in the real event
in the real rise of uh
ai maybe the real bar is higher than you
could ever imagine
you know
it's interesting it's looking more and
more like darwin's goals as a writer are
convince you that everything is getting
worse
it's impossible to stop it so give up
hope once you've given up hope then he's
going to hit you with the solution which
is
give up hope strange religionness anyway
this essay is just a trifle but he's
effective in making me give up hope yet
when i step back and ask
why this essay makes me feel hopeless it
has to do with the organs claim that
universities have been a lost cause
since 1900 or so
um yeah the
the the mythical notion that society is
always getting worse no i don't know if
i agree with i don't know if i agree
with it i
don't agree with um i don't agree with
curtis's point about paul graham's essay
i agree more with paul graham's point
after all i do want to start a college
um
uh
though i've spent a lot of time thinking
about the situation i cannot predict how
it plays out
could some universities reserve reverse
the current trend and remain places
where the independent-minded want to
congregate
or will the independent-minded gradually
abandon them i worry a lot about what we
might lose if that happened
uh curtis's response is that the
universities are a state church
and harvard yale princeton all march and
complete lockstep and all social and
political issues
uh this seems to be largely true um the
university system as a whole is lost
but the nice thing about that is
it comes in lockstep with the
university's
uh decline in actual power
um back in the day you had to take a
long time it took a long time to build
up harvard's reputation it is relatively
easy to destroy it
um i mean i agree with this uh but i'm
hopeful long-term the independent-minded
are good at protecting themselves
if existing institutions are compromised
they'll create new ones that may require
some imagination but imagination is
after all their specialty
so in a way
when i think about comma i wonder
it's a bet
on the future not looking
how the present looks and i think that
every real 100x startup has to be like
that
it's a bet basically saying that
you know what i'll make this a little
smaller so you guys can see the chat um
you guys can see so basically right now
uh laughing in the face of the ford ceo
is actually an okay
strategy um
believing that the future tactics of
business will not look anything like the
current tactics of business
uh
you know once you stop once you start
recognizing
the the seo spam all over google you
realize that it's all over business
inboxes too
11 months congratulations snorting milk
i don't agree with you the point society
is getting worse
i don't think society is getting worse
um
at all i hope that's not
um your take away from my streams
uh or actually the better one is percent
of the world
global poverty by percent of the world
um
so you know if you go back 200 years i'm
almost everybody is is living in extreme
poverty
uh whereas you fast forward today and
then here with the modernization of
china and india
um
well i don't think the world's getting
worse
i think that
if current trends continue
if current trends
go towards if we go towards the
singularity
with the current culture plex
uh we've created a terrible nightmare
for ourselves
no extreme poverty is not defined as the
worst off population it's not constant
at all
i believe extreme poverty has to do with
food insecurity
um do you have do you have the needs of
human life
uh food shelter water um
the graph is a bubble yeah population's
gonna crash bro
um yeah i mean when you look relatively
it says percent
culture is getting worse society is fine
i'm not sure about that so
a hypothesis against this book um
this book is uh
was published in 1985
um 1985
and so it's been um
uh you know it's been 35 years since
that book's been published
uh what what is being written today that
will still have relevance in 35 years
don't read anything that is is current
who's spangler who do you think who do
you think our current
rulers are
i've heard about this book
um
yeah i i don't i don't know how much i
don't know how much i buy into these
sort of theories
uh about
like decline of of of
western civilization what do you think
western civilization
is you know there's a lot of people
people talk about this this is uh
um
do you mean the enlightenment ideal of
science
uh like the enlightenment ideal
definitely will live on because it's
what wins wars
can you imagine a 15th century
army facing a modern army today
and we didn't build guns by having
better politics
they had the same politics all the
political systems
uh had largely been invented
in some way shape or form way back in
the day all right sure they
got like you know but but
we we we grew in power because of
science so i don't know what you mean
by um the decline of the west
there's an obscure correlation between
standard of living and depression
yeah yeah whatever
uh i was sitting in the uh
sitting in the barber shop i got my hair
cut and i was thinking about ubi
um wait
why is my stream lagging it's behind
way behind uh
i was thinking about uh
ubi and like if you really believe kind
of in a in a veil
but what are the two books like a theory
of justice
and like uh whatever what's nozak's book
liberty look i read these both back in
the day i just i
can never remember the name of this one
oh anarchy state utopia yeah
um
predicting the end time seems like a
popular thing to do
no i i yeah i'm certainly not predicting
the end times
um i'm saying that i think there's a
great opportunity today to create
replacements to colleges
but in some way well how would i fund it
i mean i would fund it with with common
ai money
um
but then you say well if comet ai fails
how will you fund the college
well i mean if kane high fails the world
doesn't want the college it's the same
idea
it's the same
will the
[Music]
think of let's look up the ceo of ford
right i mean not not
not to judge
you know just by looking at a picture
but you can say a bunch of things about
him looking at a picture
um
one he's relatively old two he's wearing
a suit
and three you know look at his like
bokeh effect on the picture
right like why why are you doing that
you you it i mean it says something
about you right like i wouldn't you know
i wouldn't have a picture like that
i wouldn't have i wouldn't have a it
just in a way like like
through that picture you're showing your
distance
from anything that is real right again
remember the picture of the samsung ceo
holding up the cell phone
um you could say he's a white cis male
too and there there's some
i don't know i'm not big on i'm not big
on the identity stuff
uh you know does he identify as a white
system i don't know i i think that
that's kind of a meaningless
i think that like to judge people based
on their their race or their sex or
is is just racist and sexist just it's
not
um you know it's just that in a
different form but you can certainly
judge
uh several things about him from the way
that he presents that picture the
clothes that he choose to wear in the
boca effect
right but here let's let's take a look
all right
jim hackett is president and chief
executive officer ford motor company
he's also a member of the company's
board of directors
our directors under hackett's leadership
together with bill ford
ford is committed to becoming the
world's most
trusted company
designing increasingly intelligent
vehicles that are connected to the
increasingly intelligent world
around us all to make life better for
our everyday
customers our community and our climate
the fuck does any of that mean
right i'm i'm expecting
the world that i'm expecting over the
next 10 years
about an end to this kind of stuff and
thank god for elon musk elon would never
write something like that
right let's see ceo tesla let's see if
we can actually find one on tesla.com
i'm
going to get a big list of okay here we
go
um elon musk's co-founder elites tesla
spacex neurolink the boring company
uh as co-founder and c ceo of tesla elon
leads all product design engineering and
global manufacturing of the company's
electric vehicles battery products and
solar energy products okay
um since the company's inception
in 2003 tesla's mission has been to
accelerate the world's transition to
sustainable energy
now you can say that this is very
different for
make life better for our climate
the fuck does make life better for our
climate mean
that's actually a phrase that's in here
right i'm not reading that wrong
all to make life better for our everyday
customers
our communities and our climate
like it's it's a joke it's it's almost
like
this guy knows that these people have
seen a lot of uh stock gain
so they try to like take their words and
and and and like mush them into
something
it's it's it's oh captain i need you to
activate the deflector to invert the
polar on pulse
right it's it's uh
the first test look alright so this is
just this is just like a history of
tesla
right um
but yeah i mean and then also like you
know tesla's mission has been to
accelerate and
i've seen elon talk about it and maybe
maybe the ford ceo says all this stuff
very coherently but
and i'm open to be proven wrong on this
but i doubt it right elon makes it very
clear that like you know in order to
lead the world transition and accelerate
the world transition to sustainable
energy
we have to build sexy electric cars that
can command high margin as a classic you
know classic
good business practices
um it's an ai writing not the ceo
i mean yeah so it's not
right you can say that this is actually
written by an ai but
are you saying the ceo doesn't have the
power to write something else
is is he an empty figurehead
um
yeah i think i looked at this on a
previous stream
uh wow that really ripped off uh
was it outliers
i'm not clicking a clean technical
article
uh
what would you write in my ceo page well
if anyone ever wrote something lame and
shitty
um i don't know what's on my instagram
ex iphone hacker sued by sony comma ai
president
it's my one true dream again
should i stop with the irony right like
i i guess i i i i think i believe that
my audience has the sophistication
to understand that when i say one true
dream it's like not meant to be taken
seriously
it's my one true dream to have one
million followers right and it's like
one and one i think it's like cute
um follow and be a part of hockey stick
growth right and then like you know
that's like
uh check the cover thinking fast and so
i was thinking about thinking fast and
slow you're right you're right
um
why does george present himself with it
yeah it's look is it is it my highest
quality shit i don't know man
take off the ironing no i mean it's it's
like i think it's appropriate for the
platform right
like how do you wha what is what is on
my linkedin i talk about how i use it as
a dating app and i think like that's
appropriate for that platform
all right all right all right we'll read
we'll read the clean techno art
let's let's check the biases of clean
technica
um
i write an article full of anger as a
german about the german auto industry
the octopus is one of the most
fascinating and intelligent animals in
our seas
scientists predict that if they didn't
die that early after the new generation
is born because of their ability to
learn
they would be just like the humans of
the sea dominating all other sea animals
largest
citation needed
and octopus has eight arms hence
starting with the name octo and each arm
has its own little brain managing that
on
eight brains that communicate with a
central brain
honestly this all sounds like it needs
to be refactored man refactor the
octopus
yo if we could get could we get like a
group of people
um 7 p.m uh
outside trump tower to
get some signs that say refactor the
octopus
you know what i mean like would people
would people go to that i'm not talking
about that one but just in general like
i think
i think that would just be like uh you
know think about it you'd get all these
like confused people refactor the
octopus wow they're really passionate
about it you know
um
uh i could hire people for this yeah
i'll put it on
i'll put it on craigslist ten dollars
come protest come protest the octopus
having an overly complicated
architecture
um yo
uh and free yo i actually protested for
shkreli man i protested outside the
twitter building this is like before he
went to jail and shit
to try to get him unbanned i thought it
was unfair
um he made a homage to lauren duka uh
you know plenty of kids make homages to
justin bieber and that's fine but when
he makes a collage of his love for
lauren duke it's not okay i was confused
um
free scrolling man
uh the incumbent auto industry is trying
to develop a competitive
fully electric vehicle uh
the arms are in the way yeah yeah yeah
more managers will lose their
responsibility because it's obvious that
they do not know what they do and talk
about see
i mean this is this is what i'm banking
on right if if this
is the way the world trends and most of
the things that i've said if you guys
watch the early comma ai periscopes have
largely come true
about the way this industry is going
spoiler alert
self-driving cars like level 5 are still
at least five years away at least
and that's all i'm confident to say
um
managers who in their entire life have
never written one single line of code
nor understand it all decide on vehicle
software that determines the largest
share of their profits
people who do not even know what basic
current software languages nor what it
means for success or what good code is
bad code is
good code or bad code is are deciding
the big issues they will not even
understand the problem as a software
engineer tries to explain it to them
they don't understand the challenge with
that they are far away from solving it
uh yeah this is this is right this is
again
in a way
who did they bring in to replace herbert
dice
oh he was named one of the best ceos in
the world by ceo world magazine
wasn't that the year of the volkswagen
scandal
oh yeah 2018
best ceo in the world 2019 jail
um wait
oh let's see let's see who these new guy
is
let's let's look look we can tell right
away from the picture
yeah remember what i made fun of harvard
for
the harvard ceo for it's a big picture
of a guy
in a sport coat next to a large logo of
the brand
this very clearly tells you that
volkswagen's not a car company it's a
brand
company he's not standing next to a car
here we
finally get one where there are cars in
boca
in the background right
oh yes pose with the car yes pose with
the car see
it's the brand but it's also the oh
oh i was time magazine's person of the
year in 2006 as well that's pretty cool
thank you for subscribing andy davies
um a door
yes yes we i have car please bring the
car
in here do i have to touch it with
gloves
you know really when these guys stop
wearing fucking suits i'll take them
more seriously who wears a suit anymore
could they could be real about that like
who wears a suit
like i can imagine the corny 80s movie
playing right before the like sexual
harassment goes on in the fake boardroom
scene
you know
that's why amd is so good i mean you
know
even i feel i feel a little bad for
ripping on nvidia
uh in the in the third row tesla
um but look like
at least nvidia is still run by the
founder
i think that he got a little over
excited by the money
um which like you know you can't really
blame people for that
uh you know that's when i sold my own
video and i should have huddled long
term right
um
but you know
they're they're i guess you know what i
guess i'm
they're talking to bad business advice
here if you have a five year monopoly on
ai tech exploit it
right if you have if you have a monopoly
exploit it
oh yeah yeah yeah the reckoning's coming
i've heard
the sad thing is intel's been fucked for
so long
and only now actually i guess the stop
knock going up is
pretty reflective of it
um
yeah let's see who's the intel ceo
bob swann same fucking sports coat and
bokeh bullshit
look i have people behind me
holy shit look at who's holding up a
chip
this is the picture you get of lisa sue
you see what i mean
of course they're gonna win she is so
much better just look at that
she's not wearing an ugly ass sport coat
like like she looks like she does stuff
you can just tell you just look look
look who does stuff
oh yeah this guy oh we're back to this
fucking guy
oh yeah yeah stand next to the brand
make sure the brand is in full
make sure the brand is in full is in
full uh full view
we gotta make sure they can see the
brand it's a little bokeh
i like the bokeh because i want to
emphasize that i'm the most
important thing in this shot but we also
got to let him see the brand
god no but like like do you see the
brand there
no this i mean this might make me sad if
i do lisa sue and do an image search in
order to have a fair comparison or to
really amd ceo
and do an image search
yeah better better
it's pictures with chips
chips like that's not it's like uh you
know
notice how notice how that picture like
the brand is not
neatly like put somewhere it's like a
real picture
if you google lisa sue there are more
chips
chips let's see let's see rob swann
no i got it wrong bob swan i don't know
i don't remember
all right we're done we're done ripping
on ceos um i shouldn't rip on them for
what they look like it really is kind of
a low blow
but i do want to rip on them for exactly
what's in that clean technical article
um yeah yeah the the mba offication of
the world
needs to stop these these people
are useless
like they're they're they're just
they're just exploitive psychopaths
um well i'm not coming i see you come
here doesn't have a ceo
just be honest i hate corporate culture
is it
culture yeah maybe
you got a neural link bro yeah you sign
me up bro where am i gonna when do i get
a neurolink
his job is to talk welcome to talking
hour
and you guys are gonna subscribe and pay
me yeah i get paid to talk i'm an
influencer
um
sorry about your mba bro coulda learned
real skills
how do i get unblocked from github
you're now blocked from here
congratulations
um we're we we we pull the disrespect we
just ban people sometime you know
um you can actually make crazy shit ton
of money just by talking on twitch
uh what products i use every day
this is my american passport i use it
every day
to remind myself that i have freedom
yeah i have freedom do they still have
like the constitution written in this
thing
important information regarding your
passport
we the people of the united states in
order to form a more perfect union
establish justice ensure domestic
tranquility
provide for the common defense promote
the general welfare and secure the
blessings of liberty to ourselves and
our posterity
to ordain and establish this
constitution for the united states of
america um
oh my mexico stamp mexico put the stamp
all the way in the back you know
like here my like main stamps and then
like all the way in the back is my
mexico stamp
czech's passport says don't be evil
uh
yeah i'm not i'm not a politics guy and
nationalism global i don't know anything
about that
oh incognito jam thank you for gifting
subs to people
we appreciate you
um
don't be evil is such a weird thing just
a weird thing why would they do that i
trust people who say don't be evil
uh how many countries have you visited
let's do it you want to shoot like is
there like how many countries have you
visited quiz
there's got to be like a quiz oh it's a
buzzfeed
oh let's see i've been to the u.s i've
been to mexico i've been to canada
down in south america i know i've never
been to brazil but i have been to
uruguay
argentina and chile
i've never been anywhere in africa
but i've been to spain portugal
france the united kingdom ireland
iceland never made it over to norway but
i did go to sweden didn't go to freedom
didn't go to denmark i did go belgium's
over there i've been there
germany been to italy
switzerland oh man this
zooming is oh i gotta zoom with this
all right let's see um i did these
countries once
was serbia always good old serbia
there's serbia
did not go to croatia but i did go to
hungary and i went to austria and i've
been to chechia
never been to slovakia i've been to
chechiya when it was still the czech
republic so i don't know if that counts
never been to the middle east or
uh africa but i have been
to australia i've been to japan
i've been to indonesia been to malaysia
been to thailand didn't make it to
cambodia
uh yes vietnam no philippines
yes taiwan of course china wow
wow oh there's hong kong
oh that i thought they were trying some
shit
um i've been to all the u.s states i've
been to everyone
i've been to russia
that might be it oh i've been to
mongolia i took the train up to mongolia
uh and i've been to nam haven't been to
laos
or cambodia or there or there i haven't
been to india
i haven't been to bangladesh i've been
anywhere in the middle east or to a
single stand i know i'm missing out
that's probably it
how many countries have i visited
does it not tell me
what the one thing i wanted to know
i've been to singapore yeah i guess like
yeah that's tiny down there
oh there it is singapore zooming in oh
my god really
35 countries not bad
uh probably russia and south korea for
ctfs
wow i feel like i'm like missing out on
a lot of countries
35's not so many
wow so many places i've been to panama
too
36.
oh i mean i stopped by the bahamas on a
cruise ship does that count
i think that counts 37
[Music]
and i've been to all the states nothing
too exciting
why do i avoid africa in the middle east
um
i don't know
i mean like my sister went to israel and
she's like the border was scary
uh it's like there's no there's no
real reason uh i think i am if it's
still gonna happen i'm gonna speak in
dubai
um the end of this year
i can get in i'll go there and then i've
been to the middle east
i don't know where is it going after i
just think i'd go to go to like morocco
definitely
i almost went to morocco on a trip
um i was in the bottles for a day
no i got to do so my next trip my next
trip that i'm thinking about is
these countries like i'm interested in
uh
all the plus soviet countries uh i'm
trying to find
where is there something new you know
i look like a jewish
uh africa is deadly i don't think that's
true
um i mean there's some places in africa
that are deadly but like you know so is
saint louis
uh
[Music]
yeah honduras has a really high murder
rate
uh no i'm not i'm not afraid of most
countries in africa it's not because i'm
afraid
um just kind of because like
have i been to liechtenstein no i
haven't been to liechtenstein
is that lichtenstein right there oh
luxembourg
i've never been to luxembourg either is
that liechtenstein oh my god
lichtenstein's small
i did not make it elected stein
um
where's bratty's lava
because i've definitely been to
bratislava because they oh i've been to
slovakia then
uh oh cool yeah i've been to slovakia
uh because i know i went to bratislava
because i i did
i did a train trip um up from uh
was at this conference in serbia i did a
train trip
up through here rented a car
yeah belgrade 20 20 uh
12. it's actually while i was still out
on bail
for my marijuana arrest
did i like latin america uh yeah yeah
they wouldn't let me to brazil i'd have
a visa
um switzerland i remember everything
being expensive and i wanted to draft
beer and i couldn't get one
it's hot in here boys
no i didn't go to jail it was overhyped
bullshit i was wrongfully arrested and
it's since been
dropped and expunged from my record
because i was wrongfully arrested that's
right
um wrongfully i should sue for my
wrongful arrest
uh
tell you my right that's my only time i
was ever arrested i was arrested for
marijuana in texas
nah i've never been to monaco where is
monica oh monaco is like south of france
kind of
i met some people from monaco and i was
hanging out in malaysia
oh and dora look at these little
countries
look at these tiny little countries
hmm
so i've wanted to go around the world
um by land
uh you got to kind of go through russia
i i i met this girl
in china who had done it and she went
this way
uh she was a canadian so i was like how
do you get through iran she's like i'm a
canadian they let me through
um
[Music]
i don't know how you pronounce it
um
would i go to iran i don't know if
they'd let me in
i don't know how they feel about
americans i'm cool with iran and you
know i
got i got no beef um am i even like
no they're not gonna question me at the
border and they're gonna be like why'd
you go to iran did you spend money
supporting iran
uh yeah
around the world stream what is
transinistra
whoa
this looks like definitely a war zone
frozen conflict zone
wait is this like the donuts republic
i'm sorry if i'm saying anything
offensive i honestly like i don't know
i'm not trying to be offensive
i never try to be offensive guys but
sometimes you just are offensive you see
i'm trying to be offensive but i don't
try to be inoffensive i just
say what i believe is true and if i'm
wrong
i'm happy to uh apologize for being
wrong if i'm actually wrong
if you're trying to use that i'm wrong
like a political bludgeoning tool well
you can get fucked and then i'll never
apologize
um ghana is a real nice place
where's ghana is gone a real nice place
oh west africa
no where would i actually go in africa i
definitely go to morocco
uh i go to egypt what country
is the uh mount kilimanjaro in
no i being wrong is bad you know you can
apologize for being wrong you shouldn't
be wrong
like if you're especially if you're
telling other people wrong things
like i think it's like kind of morally
not okay
i'm like if you believe wrong things and
you keep them to yourself that's fine
but if you're spreading wrong facts i
think it's morally wrong
being wrong is bad yeah
yeah misinfo's garbage right and it's
not like yeah
like like if you're if you're spreading
fake news you're bad person
conspiracy theorists are triggered right
now now some of those conspiracy
theorists
i think are on a level like
you know um look take something like
pizzagate right
like
you know it's kind of funny
in like a meta sense right like you know
you can't you can't uh
you know a lot of conspiracy theories
are pretty funny man
uh so like i'm not gonna i'm not gonna
say that's like spreading misinformation
because that doesn't purport to be
information
um it purports to be
fiction and if you can't tell that it's
fiction
well you know that's kind of on you
right um
to be fair you can almost say the same
thing about the news right
you can say the same thing about a lot
of the
i wish they would just acknowledge in
some way shape or form that they are
fictional
yeah no i mean obviously look no one's
fine with the guy who showed up with the
with the rifle right
but like that doesn't mean you know what
i mean like somebody killed john lennon
because they thought the songs were
speaking to him right that doesn't make
the songs not okay
um all right
they killed oh they oh no did not catch
her when the rye was speaking to him
right that was the guy
um watching your brand i'm not telling
you to watch your brand
how do you distinguish truth from
fiction science
uh never mind i regret using pizzagate
as an example
you fucks are too political i have to
brush up on my
on my you know 19th century conspiracy
theories that nobody actually has an
opinion on
to use as an example you can't use
modern examples it's a good it's a good
thing from less wrong
go to nagaland if you want what is naga
land
i'm learning so much
this place looks beautiful
i thought malay i thought mongolia was
going to be like beautiful jungle and it
was actually a frozen desert
that had power 23 out of the 24 hours of
the day
yeah part of the problem with can you
even make meta-political points or
metapolitical points just attract
idiots you know an interesting thing
about a topic
you know what we'll say about
programming languages because nobody's
offended by programming languages
right have you ever noticed
how like the ruby community is full of
idiots
while the haskell community is full of
people who can like write really well
is anyone offended by that oh java oh
java's the fucking worst
go to like a stack overflow about java
and like
i mean it's true clearly some
programming communities have like a
higher brow
that just this is like like like yeah
java is a good one to rip on man
[Laughter]
whatever
you know what okay all right all right
all right all right
let's let's let's um let's see um
rust uh let's ask like like
uh binary search stack overflow let's
not talk out of my ass let's use science
how would i implement a binary search
using just an array
and we're going to try this for
different languages ensure that your
array is sorted so this is the crux of
binary search any index random access
data structure can be binary search when
you say it's just an array i would say
this is a very good answer i like this
answer right
i would say this is a quality answer it
shows a recursive implementation an
iterative one
um rust high quality okay
java
[Laughter]
that was totally rust can i get some
help
please i have tried many methods to get
this to work
i got the array sorted and to print but
after that my binary search function
doesn't want to run and give me right
results
it always gives me -1 any help
just compare that to this
yo so too man let's let's let's give
ruby a fair shake
ruby binary search i'm trying to do
binary search
i get this error just use array b search
as for the error it comes from somewhere
else
it's better than java let's do
javascript
i'm trying to implement a binary search
algorithm in javascript things seem okay
but my return statements appear to be
returning undefined can anybody tell
what's wrong here
okay java ruby javascript
rust
uh well no no no no well you really
we got we got to do the
can just just just like look look at the
quality of that answer
versus this you are not actually
comparing with the array values
lowercase u
god unreadable junk
java php ruby
javascript haskell and actually i think
the rust one was the highest quality
i will do python as the last one
mid tier on par with javascript
mid-tier
why do i feel like you're about to start
a call well maybe with an apostrophe re
is there even one for agna
oh my god wow
and it only got one up vote
okay ag agna is really top tier
the tricky part is understanding what
the widening function actually needs to
change once you've got that right in the
code is fairly easy
and then proceeds to write a really nice
happy coding
beautiful english well formatted
yo and agnes god your language
[Music]
all right guys we're getting near the
end
of this
yeah there's probably only 10 active
devs in the world and i mean though this
says something about
well that gets into deep truths
all right any q a
google programming languages as weapons
i know i was short with you guys last
night
um what the fuck i can't even
[Laughter]
this is pretty good rust is a 3d printed
gun it may work
someday
it's usually only used because how shiny
it is
this is good these are good
c sharp is a powerful laser rifle
strapped to a donkey
who takes off the donkey the place it
doesn't seem to work as well
uh lisp is a ship which comes in many
forms anyone who uses this is probably
crazy and dangerous
refactoring freebsd kernel
yeah i don't know whoever they switched
from c plus plus to java
i was the last year that took the ap
compsci test in c
plus um
i'm done with the merge sort reform
board with that
uh oh my god is neural link going to be
the next gbt3
you guys are all going to ask about yeah
i talked about neuralink already i
talked about that in an old stream
do i still work i worked hard this week
i made i made dollars boys
i made dollars
thank you i hope i don't want to
zuckerbergy you know
i did say things about gbg3
not disrupting nobody's social shit man
there's collaborators there's dissidents
and then there's the detach
i'm going to one of those 10-day vip
asana retreats
you know and leave you guys all with the
world that you made man you know
i didn't do it that's i didn't do
nothing man
deep dive into nuclear physics and boss
at google was
interested in like reactor design you
know a bit about it
like molten salt reactors and stuff what
do you mean like like
like the equations behind nuclear
physics
which i kind of know like yeah the
uranium splits and gives off this and
the neutron
uh no it was a contract
yo kodak gets it remember when kodak was
a blockchain company
and now they're a covid company
common connect pivots to drugs after
abandoning photography and crypto
no not bug bounties bug bounties are for
bitches
it is a great title
nick bogo sort updates on hammer
hammer became political and that's why
it was canceled just like this stream
would be
if anybody made a fucking discord
um
oh grow my long curly hair i look like
tom hanks i'll take that man tom hanks
good looking guy
i don't know about the mark zuckerberg
have you tried quantum programming not
really i heard like some new language
came out
and i
like i don't know is there like a good
language for this
it sounds kind of fun
sorry strawberry field ai uh
most of what i know about quantum i
learned from reading uh quantum
computing system archites
oh god midflowmax caught yeah
maybe at the very height of my
competitive programming career
i could write that i can't anymore
inline gifs in terminal that's way too
terry davis
here pie quill
righty computing wait
wasn't that the kid from silicon valley
but the other guy the kid who did
nothing big head
why did i think his his name was
righetti
big heady oh close
oh my god man you know this thing's a
scam
this is a fucking steampunk quantum
computer
i don't know the pi quote might not be a
scam now all i'm saying is
if that's what they're advertising on
their website
um
yeah are quantum computers real
let's google it i don't believe they are
but i i don't believe they're impossible
and i believe they will be built
once yeah yeah okay quantum supremacy i
don't even
i didn't really follow that because it's
all like i don't want to read scientific
america
well maybe scientific americans okay
let's take a look
well i'm judging the quality of the
article based on how many interruptions
they have and that one
um this is kind of old so
first step is to make quantum chips
5 trillion transistors to simulate 42
cubits
i mean that seems right what's 2 to the
42.
yeah like 5 trillion
but that's assuming quantum computers
can solve mp complete problems they
absolutely cannot
oh great the us health subcommittee on
bullshit um oh what might have to do
with ai nothing
are quantum like i would believe
i will you unfollowed essay after they
show the metric system
you apple pie yankee guy
probably measures their dick size and
fahrenheit
you know
what do i think about p and np you
i don't know if you guys uh
yo actually i'm gonna chill for this
well so okay first
um you want to watch a good video
if you guys haven't seen this
[Music]
then his dad looked over his mom and
said you know this is probably less time
we're going to see
[Applause]
speaks russian americans
chose
[Applause]
you're about to see a russian air strike
on syrian ranks they inferior to
amphibious siberian tanks
you're nothing but a civilian with sileo
blanks
who's really up his own ass like azealia
banks
but then what's more unreal and this is
the quote that i'm gonna leave you with
uh
yes
foreign
you know that's how i feel
that is how i feel man i would rather
die of fucking no name than become
famous and end up being like you
that's how i feel though you know
you say that now you know what bro if i
ever don't say that
here we go
i'd rather look at no name than mw
famous and end up being like you
if i ever don't say that or um this was
on ella's blog
uh
she had like reminder from childhood
um when i was a child adults often
didn't treat me well
they didn't seem to care about my
feelings would do things that made me
really sad and generally dismissed my
experience of the world is less
important because i was a child a fact
that they reminded me of constantly
i didn't know how to communicate to them
how much this hurt me but this was
seriously confusing to me because
they've been children once right
and they talked about their bad
childhood sometimes which mean they had
once been in my position
i realized all the children had grown up
into adults then turned around and
stopped caring about children's feelings
because they'd forgotten what it was
like to be a child this terrified me
mainly because i knew that one day i
would become an adult too would i grow
up and forget
would i do this exact thing to the next
generation of children's
so i packaged a mental message for my
future self
a set of impressions that i would
remember regularly as the years went on
and preserve over time
as close to its original form as i could
manage the message went something like
this
you don't remember what it's like to be
a child but i'm telling you
take the experience of children
seriously don't underestimate how real
and how important this is
don't forget me i'm an adult now and
i've mostly forgotten i'm not around
kids very much
my memories are fuzzy but that message
sent from my childhood is still very
vivid in my mind
so you say i say that now
not a public figure
wanna see some real
i've been a public figure for a long
time
um and fuck that shit
you do not want to be famous
so i'm telling you i'm a public figure
i'm a guy who streams and a bunch of
y'all watch me no
if i win self-driving cars if kama wins
self-driving cars
i won't be famous
like think about the kind of person
who's famous you know people think
people think i'm an egomaniac right
people think oh yeah joha you know he
sticks his name in his face on
everything like
i don't know i mean you know why did i
stick my face in the jail breaks like
for me it was just like funny like the
irony
the irony and i didn't really you know i
was young i didn't really like get it at
the time
right i didn't get like the irony of
branding
like it was it was a joke like it wasn't
meant to be it was it was it was a
hacker
like um
you know did it look like a real like
just just you know it was it was funny
and i didn't
get
i i guess i didn't get what i was making
fun of at the time
now i want to speak russian i want i
want to understand like
like
the level
in this in this in this rap battle
um uh if language structure thought
these people have access to language i
don't have
um oxymoron tells the story
shit i gotta read this the hero with a
thousand
faces yes
oh it's an anthology
all right this is what i'll read next
you know i read this
junior year english class i had some
some camel essays
you can learn this cyrillic alphabet in
two hours i've tried
i can't i'm not like good at things like
that
um though i was trying to
[Applause]
stop
i've been trying i mean i i i spent a
morning on that
russian sounds like i'm reading the
torah um
oh my god the book of why does judea
pearl pay you to come in here and
chill
uh oh try this in your free time all
right cool
and that's how i feel man
oh god i don't i don't know man oh no
that's why i gotta click you know like
if you ask me to do the same thing with
that i can't do that because i don't
know how to
you know oh shit i don't know
um
but yeah
i just i just
you guys can remember this is the end of
this stream you know it's forever on the
internet uh
that
who's pavel durov i've heard that name
before
i've definitely watched disaster or an
oxymoron it's sad how badly he beats him
um it's almost like disaster isn't
playing for all the marbles and oxymoron
is
uh thanks gig effect
oh no i've never met him
travel the world in self-imposed exile
and then are they in america they're
here in uh new york
i mean where would you go you know
uh well if anyone knows him i'm down i'm
about to hang out
um
bald and bankrupt
no i don't know this guy's a blogger
he's a blogger oh damn
oh russia beyond
foreigners show you the real russia
who's forced to apologize on camera
by chechnyan authorities
oh my god yo i love when people have
real experiences on youtube so i don't
have to
bald and bankrupt is a creep and a sex
pest
hey i don't know i don't know anything
about this guy
all right guys
we're gonna we're gonna finish the
quantum we're gonna look into quantum
python
i think i like look downloaded this once
before
is it a cute is it like a nice paradigm
of learning
this website looks crappy
q sharp is it a microsoft language
dude are they fucking kidding me
fuck google
oh no this is like this isn't
yep it was sad yeah they gave me q anon
bullshit yup
you know guys the companies don't care
man people are always saying oh
the search engines all the social media
companies they have a liberal bias no
they have an
outrage bias they have an idiocy bias
if it's dumb they give it to you
uh my solidity changes got merged in
that's nice
video buffering
not even majority bias it's like if
there's something that can like you know
be
dumb yet outrage you
no i'm not making a hammer i'm out man
my stand in the culture wars i'm going
to build a college
that's my stand in the culture war
who cares what it is the difference
between q anon and pizzagate
is q anon takes itself you know what
never mind fuck it
no i'm not i'm not talking about this
it's all bullshit guys
it's all bullshit it's just thinking
about it rot your brain you know
will i actually make a college or is the
college like the church
well the problem with the church no look
don't take me that don't hold me that
accountable right
the college on the level of seriousness
here's comma ai
here's hammer here's backspace and
here's the college
comma ai college backspace hammer
was that tribalism it's the incentives
of these companies
tribalism's always existed the
incentives of these companies has not
you can't even blame the companies it's
just the incentives i don't know you
know
all they can come into smash is power
um the college requires a entrance exam
um and the entrance exam you'll sit for
it right at the college
and then we'll set a threshold on the
entrance exam and everybody who does
better than that threshold is welcome to
attend
the problem with the college is that
it's already the church no you can't
make a church because it turns out only
crackpots want to make churches
now if you want to make proper tinder
you have to charge men money
i don't understand why dating apps don't
do this
dating apps are terrible because it's a
sausage fest and it's a sausage fest
because it costs the same for men and
women
you want to charge men money every club
promoter knows this you do not want your
club to be full of dick
so you charge men money i don't know why
dating apps don't do this
we'll be on the exam intelligence
nothing you can't study for it
there will not be a physical assessment
now
it's an entrance exam
if app charged money there would only be
rich ugly guys
i don't think that's true i'm not saying
a lot of money right just enough money
that you want
so i think what you'd end up with right
like if you sign up go sign up as a girl
on
i did this back in the day on okcupid
sign up as a girl and realize all the
spam you get
you get tons of messages from guys but
that's the only strategy they have
because they
you know this is the strategy you have
to use on dating websites you have to
mass spam messages
and this is because the ratios are super
imbalanced right
um imagine you know you can imagine the
physical instantiation of this is a club
right
do club only have rich the clubs only
have rich ugly guys
i don't really think so
oh my god bumble oh i went in some
horrendous dates from bumble fuck that
website
um
instagram instagram is the best dating
app that's true the dms boys
the dms you know oh the dms
fuck tinder man
dating is i mean it's a lot easier it's
easy in new york
uh that dating is great
find dates on twitch i've looked at the
demographics of my
audience i am
i am straight um
i've never actually gotten a date off of
linkedin
um let's just say i have standards
and the messages i have actually gotten
do not meet
uh my standards
uh what about grindr i think it work i
mean again
if you're into i think it works i think
the gay dating apps work a lot better
um because of the fundamental symmetry
well tinder sucks yeah of course a
tinder you can't use tinder anymore
i'm not on tinder um tinder still works
in some countries tinder worked well
like in malaysia
i had some luck with tinder i mean i had
luck with tinder like way back in the
day
go back to like 2012. tinder still
worked
now it's a meme hinge
hinges so you got to get past the cringy
questions
uh no i don't even think i don't even
think tinder works if you work out
um what was wrong with bumble i don't
want i yeah
yeah i'm not going to go into what's
wrong with bumble
columbus i don't know people found dates
on clubhouse
this one looks like the best this kisket
is it python
sorry we're making the uh making the me
tiny again
uh okay so i mean dating sites suck just
go meet the person face to face stop
using useless tools so
uh while having conversation i mean your
dating apps are just funnels right
i mean it's it's you know you really you
want to build they saw
man you know so many i've given you so
many company ideas today uh build like a
crm for dating like build
salesforce for dating
seeking arrangement follows the one rule
it charges men money
uh you have to charge men money
i think that that didn't do what i
wanted
i might regret using pseudo
i finished for loops boys
well yeah but fake accounts i mean fake
accounts would go away with uh
yeah so you'd need i mean you'd want
you'd want to make sure
that look if people if i'm charging 50
bucks a month for an account
or 30 bucks a month for an account uh it
doesn't matter
um if people make fake ones or not you
can waste your money on that
uh yeah for the women who get free
accounts you're gonna want uh
verification
the girls in sd are better than ny i
don't know about that boys
i don't know about that
simple ratios you know
uh what do they say in the hunger games
uh
the odd may the odds be forever in your
favor
well that's new york
let's convert hammer into a dating
website
yo it's a search for people
it's a search engine for people
yeah yeah and then it'll like pre-write
your first messages it'll arrange you
i mean i mean that's the crm of dating
right like you know if you guys use
dating apps seriously and
there's you can succeed with dating apps
um if you use dating apps seriously
you get you basically build a sales
phone
to go back into a dating app
organizing the world's humans i think
talent here has got us beat
we're trying a little bit with the
quantum
we're casually doing things boys we're
doing things
i mean yeah can gvt3 write how okay how
do you get access to the gbd3 api
gpd2 online we'll settle for gpt too
oh this is the one that's taken down
though
man
ah get started by writing a custom um
what is a good
opening uh
message for to send
to a girl on
a dating app
tab
ah well in one moment it's the perfect
one to receive
honestly if you sent that message on a
dating app it might get you some
interesting replies
i can say i've heard the word ah in our
minds
a quick reply a hint an email just a
couple of simple and very
let us know in the comments
this key can be used
i don't know
say some dumb crap that normies will
find deep
um yeah no i think we're going to need
gvd three level technology
okay all right all right we're going to
apply
we're going to apply seriously join
waitlist i'm interested in being a beta
user of the api
george hearts geohot plus hammer
gmail.com we're going to turn hammer
into a uh
your use case
spend a lot
of time messaging
many people
on dating
apps this
can be replaced
by ai i'm interested in receiving email
updates about the api
yes but only if i get hammer
hammer.law this can be replaced by
ai
this would benefit
society because
more true love
can be found
more efficiently
that's it this is not this is not for
hammer let's just let's just let's just
do geohot
a more true love this can be replaced
by a good we want to be accepted
good ai language model like
gbt3 always flatter the authors this
would benefit society because more
true love can be found more efficiently
there may be
risks if the
ai sends in
appropriate
oh i got i don't know how to spell in
a propriet messages
or if
if
people weren't
really looking for true
love and actually
actually
just enjoyed
messaging people
this can replace by a good ai language
model
combined with
with a crm
like salesforce
perfect men spend a lot of time
messaging people on dating apps
this can be wait we shouldn't be gender
exclusive
people spend a lot of time messaging
many people on dating apps this can be
replaced
by a good ai language model like gpg3
let's just leave it at that we don't
need to talk about the cr this would
benefit society
because more true love can be found more
efficiently
there may be risks if the ai sends
inappropriate messages or if people
weren't really looking for true love
we'll just leave it at that
perfect who thinks i'll be approved
[Laughter]
who thinks i'll be approved
i talked about the benefits and risks of
society
i promise they won't i read that you
know
the good news is i have access to a
super computer if i want it on gbt3 is a
little big
we'll try yeah sure we'll do it on
stream if i'm approved go go email open
ai and tell them to let me in but be
polite
you remember you're representing the
george hot's twitch channel
inappropriate messages yo
ask your dick pic
no but really really just imagine a gpt
that's scheduled just imagine like it
just schedules your dates for you
you don't have to do all that
pre-messaging you know a lot of sites
have like
even the better sites of like a 21 ratio
you got to send out 20 messages for
every date you go on
um this is a christian channel i'm
trying to help people find true love
more efficiently
oh whoa well that's too deep man those
people don't want to you don't know it's
not them man it's not them you know
pot suits
uh yeah i should try out ai dungeon i
hear you sign up you got the thing
hello mr altman i'm representing mr ox
[Music]
all right all right that was we we had
fun uh
i don't know i might go look at quantum
stuff off stream i'm kind of interested
but on stream this stream has been wow
we just did we just did
two and a half hours of just talking you
know
i hope you guys enjoyed the talking
stream
thank you all for watching
uh
please subscribe if you enjoy this
content
if you're not a subscriber uh i look at
how much money i make off twitch
and it decides how much i'm going to
stream
that's not really true but it's kind of
true
good vibes thank you all for watching be
the change you want to see in the world
that's bad advice just be that's good
advice
bye everybody